Guide to the Amos Poe Papers, 1966-2005 MSS.203
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Writing
  - Series I, Subseries B: Film Treatments, Notes and Notebooks
    - "The Suitacase" by Amos Poe [Partial with Notepad], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - "Tar Baby" Synopsis by Willy Rameau [With Notes], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - "Tar Baby" Treatment [Handwritten], undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - "Thespians" by Amos Poe [Pitch, Synopsis], undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "The Tides: Outs" [Notes, Etc.], undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - "To Kill An Angel" Treatment, April 12, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "To Kill An Angel" Treatment, c1986 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "To Kill An Angel" [Draft Notes, Etc.], undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - "Tomesha" Treatment, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Script Corrections], July 6, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Script Notes], undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - "Troika" / "Round Trip" [Treatment], undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - "Tsunami" by Amos Poe [Treatment with Related Documents], c2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - "12 Things That Beginning Writers Should Do", undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - "Unmade Beds" Sequences #23 - 24 [With Photographs], undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - "Unsportsmanlike Conduct" by Amos Poe [Synopsis], undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - "Untitled" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - [Untitled Notepad], undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "Voodou Child (A.K.A. Rules of the Road" by Amos Poe [With Notes], 1995 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - "The Warhol Trilogy" Treatment by Amos Poe, March 1997 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Series I, Subseries C: Source and Subject Files
    - "Acid Baseball" [Research, Etc.], 2002 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Arslanian, Melvie, c1991 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - [Assorted Postcards], undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - [Assorted Visual Source Material, 1 of 2], undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
      This assortment of source material was originally housed in a metal film can.
    - [Assorted Visual Source Material, 2 of 2], undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - [Assorted Visual Source Material], various (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - [Assorted Visual Source Material], various (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Charlesworth, Sarah, various (Box 14, Folder 39)
      Oversize materials from this subject file were removed for proper housing. Please see corresponding oversize series for contents.
    - Clemente, Alba, undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Coltrane, Robbie [Includes Photographs], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "Dead Time" [Research], c2000 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - "Deer Isle" [Jokes, Politics], 2001 - 2003 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Driver, Sara, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - "Einstein" [Research], 2002 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - "Euro Trash": European Trash Cinema Video Catalog [With Updates, Etc.], 2001 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - "Fernando" [Research], various (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Films of Andy Warhol, The Whitney Museum, c1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Hannah, Duncan, various (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Hell, Richard, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Heyman, John [1 of 2], 1991 - 2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Heyman, John [2 of 2], 1997 - 2005 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Jarmusch, Jim, various (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "John the Cop" [Crime Index Cards #1001 - 1100], undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
      These elements were originally housed in the Agent Breaker Petty Cash Tin, Object ID #: 203.2.0011.
    - "John the Cop" [Crime Index Cards #1101 - 1200], undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - "John the Cop" [Crime Index Cards #1201 - 1280], undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "John the Cop" [Criminal Law Flash Cards], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - "John the Cop" [Fireman Headline Index Cards #F1 - F21], c1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - "John the Cop" [Headlines Index Cards], 1989 - 1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - "John the Cop" [Research], 1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Kaufman, Phyllis, 1996 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - "Kid Killer" [Research], 1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - "Kid Killer" [Research], 1993 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - "Kid Killer" [Research], c1993 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Kral, Ivan, various (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Kubrick, Stanley, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - "La Pacifica" [Research], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - "The Ladies' Man" by Richard Price [With Amos' Notes], 1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      The white paper elements represent locations of interest. Please do not remove.
    - "Love at 30" [Research], c1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Mitchell, Eric, various (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - "Movie Ideas" [Clips of Interest], various (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Research], undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - "Night Witches": "Aircraft of WWII" by Stewart Wilson, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      The white paper elements in this book represent locations of interest. Please do not remove.
    - "Night Witches": "Atlas of World War II" by Richard Natkiel, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - "Night Witches": "Barbarossa" by Alan Clark [With Notes], 1965, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "Night Witches": "Jane's Fighting Aircraft of World War II," Foreword by Bill Gunston [With Notes], 2001 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      The paper elements in this book represent locations of interest. Please do not remove.
    - "Night Witches": "Love Stories of World War II" Compiled by Larry King, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "Night Witches": "Luftwaffe: A History," Edited by Harold Faber, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Night Witches": "Luftwaffe At War, German Bombers Over Russia" by Manfred Griehl, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Night Witches": "Museums of New York, Special Design Issue, Volume 8, #1", Winter 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Night Witches": "The Second World War: A History" by Martin Gilbert [Revised Edition], 1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - "Night Witches": "Stalingrad: A Pictorial History", 2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - "Night Witches": "Time Life Books: Red Army Resurgent World War II", 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - "Night Witches": "War In The Air" by Stephen Coonts, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Night Witches": "War In The Air, 1914 - 45" by Williamson Murray, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Poe, Amos, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Porges, Sandra, various (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Price, Richard, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - "Quotes", undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - "Rent" [Playbill and Clips of Interest], c1996 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "The Revolution Is Under Construction" [Research], c1999 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - "Save Our City" [Research], 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "Spanish Steps" [Research and Notes], c2004 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Starr, Steven, c1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "Vogueing" [Research], various (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Wittenborn, David, various (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Yacht Cruise" [Research], various (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Zeitgeist Film Catalog, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Series I, Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - "A Season In Hell" A Translation by Cristobal Colon [With Annotation], undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - "Acid Baseball" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Acid Baseball: A Novel" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - [Address Book], undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - "All My Life I Had To Write Letters" [Herzlish, Israel], 1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "Amos Poe Interview" by Betty Sussler [With Annotation], undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - "Amos Poe" for Cover Magazine, #5, March 26, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - "Amos Poe Interviews Amanda Donohue for BOMB", undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - "Animated Cartoon 'Great Inventions, Part 1...' " by Frank Robbins [1st Draft], undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - [Appointment Book], 1978 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - [Appointment Book], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - [Appointment Book], 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - [Appointment Book], 1982 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - [Appointment Book], 1983 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - [Appointment Book], 1984 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - [Appointment Book], 1986 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - "Belinda" A Short Story by Amos Poe, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - "Berlin Confidential" [Notebook], 1982 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - "Brain Fragment / From Papers Found on the Body of Moro" by Amos Poe, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - "Brando, Garbo, Crusoe, Poe" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - "Business Plan 2005" Amos Poe, Rain Films, March 30, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - "The Capitalist," A Provocation by Amos Poe, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - [Composition Notebook], 1969 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - [Composition Notebook], c1970 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - "Contact", Undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - "The Correct Sadist" by Terence Sellers [With Annotation], undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - [D.H. Lawrence Composition Notebook], 1970 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - [Downtown Articles by Amos Poe], 1976 - 1979 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - "The End of the Last Rebellion" and "The Parisian Suicide Mission of Eddie Caine" by Stanley Moss, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - "Folklore and Folklife Studies" by Laurence Lippsett, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - "The Highland Gardens" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - "The Hocking County Jail: Thoughts From Within [Poems], undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - "How To Make A Movie" by Amos Poe for High Times Magazine, May 1978 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - "In the Belly of the Beast" [Poems], undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - [India 1976 Planner and Address Book] (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - "Interview with Tony Spiridakis" by Amos Poe, December 27, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - "Italian X-Rays" [Lyrics, Poems], undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - "Informally Spacey: An Interview with Kevin Spacey" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - "La Pacifica, Book 1: Don't Ask Why" by Joel Rose and Amos Poe, Art by Tayyar Ozkan, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - "La Pacifica, Book 2: Serpent's Progress" by Joel Rose and Amos Poe, Art by Tayyar Ozkan, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - "La Pacifica, Book 2: Serpent's Progress" by Joel Rose and Amos Poe, Art by Tayyar Ozkan, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - "La Pacifica, Book 3: Sucker's End" by Joel Rose and Amos Poe, Art by Tayyar Ozkan, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - "La Pacifica" [Editorial Presentation], 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - "La Pacifica" [Fragments], 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - "La Pacifica" [Writer Rights and Agreement], March 26, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - [Lyrics], c1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Lyrics by Mark Malkas, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Naked Across the Prairies" by Amos Poe, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - "1968: A Teen's Journey to Filmmaking", undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - [Notebook: Lyrics, Poetry], undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - [Notebook / Scrapbook], 1992 - 1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - "NY Talk" by Amos Poe [Reviews], 1985 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - "On the Shore of Lake Kinneret" by Amos Poe for The Village Voice, April 17, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - "The Other Side (of the door)" and "A Fishing Memory" by Amos Poe, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - "Penny's Bowie" by Amos Poe, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - [Pocket Notebook], undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - [Pocket Memo Book], undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - [Poems and Essays by Amos Poe], 1968 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - [Poems, Lyrics], 1975 - 1976 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - [Poems and Story Synopsis by Amos Poe], 1975 - 1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - [Poems, Lyrics by Amos Poe], undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - [Poetry Notepad], undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - "Ramblings" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - [Red Memo Book], undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - [Short Stories by Amos Poe], 1975 - 1978 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo and Queenborough Community College Notebook, Poetry and Notes], undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo Philosophy Notebook], undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo Psychology Notebook], undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - "Table of Thoughts..." by Amos Poe, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - "Thoughts!" by Amos Jay Porges, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - ["To AP Love SC" Notebook], c1985 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Writers Guild of America East Members' Handbook, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Series II: Production Files
  - Series II, Subseries A: Administrative
    - "Agent Breaker" by Steven Starr [4th Draft with Revisions and Blocking/Staging Plans], October 1, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Crew Lists, Resumes, and Related Documents], 1991 - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Legal], 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Location Memos], 1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Memos, Etc.], 1991 - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Misc. Production], 1991 - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Notes], 1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Post Production Memos], 1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Shooting Schedules], October 1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - "Alphabet City" [Call Sheets], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - "Alphabet City" [Casting: "Angie Possibilities from LA"], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - "Alphabet City" [Casting: "Photos Sent to Amos"], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - "Alphabet City" [Contact Lists and Interview Lists], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - "Alphabet City" [Daily Log], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - "Alphabet City" [Green Binder, Misc. Production], c1983 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - "Alphabet City" [Misc: Looping Charts, Etc.], c1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - "Alphabet City" [Misc. Production], c1983 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - "Alphabet City" [Script Log with Production Report and Wild Track], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - "Alphabet City" [Shooting Schedule], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - "Alphabet City" [Shot List], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - "Alphabet City" ["Shot Lists / One Liners"], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - The American Film Institute: Independent Filmmaker Program Guidelines, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Animotion: "I Engineer" [Music Video Concept Notes], 1986 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Animotion: "Obsession" [Shot List, Etc.], undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Ballad Energy Systems, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - "Berlin Confidential" [Misc. Production], c1982 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Notes, Various] (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Cameo: "Attack Me With Your Love" [Contracts], 1985 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Cameo: "Single Life" [Music Video, Giant Steps], 1985 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - "Cold Case Files" [Development, Contracts, Etc.], c1999 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - "Compilation Film" [Meeting Minutes], November 17, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Casting], 1993 - 1994 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Casting], 1993 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Continuity Log], 1995 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Development, Etc.], 1993 - 1994 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - "Dead Weekend" [IRS Pictures, Deal Memo], c1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Misc. Production], 1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Shot List], August 29, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Storyboard Sketches], undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - "Die Tomorrow" [Storyboard Cards, Notes], undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - "Doc Savage" [Rights], 1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - "Earthly Possessions" [Final Crew Lists, Etc.], 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - "Enter the Masters" [Purchase Agreement], 1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - [Equipment Instruction Manuals], 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - "The Foreigner" [Patti Astor Contract], 1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - "The Foreigner" [Various Production], c1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Casting: Headshots], c1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Casting: Notes], c1994 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Casting: WGA Headshots], undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Clearances], June 21, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Crew Resumes, A - L], c1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Crew Resumes, M - Z], c1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Deal Ammendments, TSG Financing], 1996 - 1997 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Deal Memo Drafts], 1996 -1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [End Title Credit Memo], 1997 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Main Title Credits], August 15, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Monologue Shooting Order], June 20, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Production Checklist], May 5, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Schedules], 1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Shooting Script, Pink Revision], June 23, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Shot Lists], June 30, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Synopsis and Site Breakdown], May 6, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Various Production] (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Various Production] (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - "Generous Heart" [Development], 1992 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - "Golden Eagle" [Writer's Agreement], 1992 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - "Gone Fishin' " [Production Agreement], 1993 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - "The Grey Nun" [Development], 1994 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - "The Guitar" [Cating, Etc.], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "The Guitar" ["Notes and Taxes"], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "The Guitar" [Phyllis Kaufman Notes], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - "The Guitar" [Shooting Schedules, Etc.], 1999, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "The Guitar" [Story Notes, Casting Notes], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - "Hard On Berlin" [Momo Photos and Notes], c1988 - 1991 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - "Hunger" [Development], 1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - John Parr: "Naughty Naughty" [Shot List], undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - "John the Cop" [Misc. Production], c1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - "John the Cop" [Personal Release Forms], undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - "John the Cop" [Transcripts, Release Forms, Interview Management], 1996 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - "John the Cop" [Various] (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - "John the Cop" [Various], c1996 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Juice Newton: "Can't Wait All Night", 1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - "Kenny Makes A Move" [Various], c2004 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - "Kid Killer" [Casting], 1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - "Kid Killer" [Location Materials], 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - "Kid Killer" [Notes], 1993 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - "Kid Killer" [Shot Schedule], undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - "Ladies' Man" [Misc.], 2004 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - "Ladies' Man" [Showtime], c2001 - 2003 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - "La Pacifica" [Rights Agreement, Writer], 1993 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - "The Listener" [Deal Memo], 1993 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - "The Listener" [Memorandum of Agreement], 1993 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - "The Listener" [Misc.], various (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - "Love At 30" [Meeting Notes], 1985 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Martin Briley: "Dangerous Moments", undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - "Most Likely to Succeed" [Agreements], 2002 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Casting], 1990 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Contracts, Etc.], 1996 - 1997 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Rights Agreement], 1991 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Various], 1991 - 1996 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - "Night Witches" [Development], 2001 - 2002 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - "Paint It Black" [Agreements], 1987 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Poe Productions: Contacts, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Poe Productions: Copyright, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Poe Productions: Minute Book, Certificate Book, Stock Ledger, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Poe Productions: Polygram / Island Music Publishing Group Catalog, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Poe Productions: Polygram / Island Music Publishing Group Catalog Media [CDs], 1992 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Poe Productions: Resumes, various (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Poe Productions: Resumes, various (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Poe Productions: Writers Guild of America East Pamphlets, various (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - "Port of Call" [Casting], 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Rain Film: [Various Projects], c1992 - 1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Raven: "On and On" [Shooting Schedule, Etc.], undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - "The Revolution Is Under Construction" [Contracts, Agreements], 1999 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Casting], July 16, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Daily Production Log Book], undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Day Breakdown, Etc.], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Memorandums, Agreements], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" ["Production Information"], undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Resumes], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Shooting Schedules], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Staff and Crew Lists], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Storyboard Segments], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Various], 1986 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Run DMC: "You Talk Too Much", undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - The Runaways: "Cherry Bomb", undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - "Save Our City" [Development], 1992 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - "Scarlet Lips" [Agreement], 1988 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - "See No Evil, Hear No Evil (Theresa Stern Story)" [Shooting Schedule], 1988 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - "7 x 7" [Various], 1985 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Steve Earle: "Jerusalem", October 2002 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Steve Earle: "Just An American Boy", 2002 - 2005 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Steve Earle: "Some Other Plans" [Log Book], undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Steve Earle: "Transcendental Blues", 2000 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Steve Earle: "Untitled Long Form" [Release Forms], 2002 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - "Stunning" [Various], c1999 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - "Subway Riders" [Contracts], various (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - "Subway Riders" [Motion Picture - Television Permit Application], 1980 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - "Subway Riders" [Various], undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - "The Theresa Stern Story" [Contract], January 1, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - "To Kill An Angel" [Development], c1998 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Cookie Mueller School Fund], 1991 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Contract], May 15, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Independent Feature Market], c1991 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Original Extended Contract], May 15, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Taft Contract], May 15, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Various], 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - "29 Palms" [Emails, Shot Schedule Notes], 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - "29 Palms" [Development], 2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - "29 Palms" [Master Editing and Reshoot List, Etc.], c2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - "29 Palms" [Music Memorandums], 2001 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - "Underage" [Various], 1998 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - "Unmade Beds" [Image/Shot Sheet], undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - "Unmade Beds" [Sequence Inserts], June 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - "Untitled / When You Find Me" [Various], c2003 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Van Stephenson: "What the Big Girls Do", 1984 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - [Various Projects: Outlines, Etc.], 1994 - 1998 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - "Vogueing" [Writing Agreement], 1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - "Warhol" [Various], 1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Yomo Toro: "Noveleo", 1990 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Series II, Subseries B: Financial